Contact

03122533963 (Mobile) imran_shah20@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/imran-shaha695122a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ASP.NET
HTML
CSS

Languages

English (Limited Working)
Urdu (Elementary)
Pashto (Elementary)

Imran Shah

Senior Software Engineer at Intellexal Solutions Private Limited Pakistan

Summary

I'm .NET Developer with 4+ years of working experience in Web Programming, Front-end and Back-end.

Skills:

Languages: C# ,JavaScript ,HTML ,HTML5 ,CSS &

CSS3,Ajax,JSON

Frameworks: Asp.net MVC, Asp.net Web Forms

Front-end Libraries or Frameworks : Bootstrap , Jquery

Database Tools: Microsoft SQL Server 2016 ,2014

Service: Microsoft Web API, WCF

Others: JIRA, Postman, ASP. NET Web Forms, Desktop Application Development, Windows Forms, Payment Gateways integrations,

Agile Methodologies.

Source Control: GIT

Experience

Intellexal Solutions Private Limited Senior Software Engineer January 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

e-square-HR services Software Engineer January 2019 - January 2020 (1 year 1 month) karachi.Pakistan

Viftech Solutions (Pvt.) Ltd. Software Engineer January 2018 - January 2019 (1 year 1 month) karachi

worked as a junior software engineer

AQM Solutions

Junior Software Engineer April 2017 - December 2017 (9 months)

Karachi Pakistan

Coordinate Develop & manage multiple IT projects.

Developed Web forms in ASP.NET using C# as the Code-behind language and JQuery as a Front end language.

Developed Master Pages.

Responsible for understanding user requirements, de signing

a n d developing the application.

Involved in the development of Presentation Logic for GUI of ASP.NET pages

Freelance Website Developer Web Developer July 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 1 month) karach

Education

Shaheed Zulfikar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology Master of Science - MS, Computer Software Engineering (2018 - 2020)

Iqra University (Official)
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2012 - 2016)

Govt.College For Men Nazimabad Computer Science · (2010 - 2012)